Now I'm going to introduce you to
现在我要向你们介绍
Jupyter notebooks. Notebooks are an amazing
这些笔记本是一种令人惊奇的东西
tool for data analysis, where text, code,
数据分析工具 其中文本 代码,
and images all sit in one document in your
和图像都坐在一个文件在你的
browser.
浏览器
Here's an example notebook where I
这里有一个例子
explored predicting body fat percentage
探索预测身体脂肪百分比
with various regression models. Up top
各种回归模型 上面
here you see what's called a text cell.
这里你可以看到所谓的短信
Cells are these guys and they can contain text
细胞就是这些家伙 它们可以包含文本
or code. If I double-click on the text
或代码 如果我双击文本
cell, I can edit the text in here. It's
我可以在这里编辑文本
written in markdown, a text format with
以减价书写 一种文本格式
syntax that renders to HTML. So for instance,
例如,
if I want to write a link, this is the
如果我想写一个链接 这是
syntax for it, and if I render the
语法 如果我渲染
text, it's a link. This is a code cell.
文本 它是一个链接 这是一个代码单元格
You can see here I'm importing some
你可以看到我正在进口一些
packages like Numpy and Pandas. I can run
像 Numpy 和 Pandas 这样的包裹 我可以跑
this cell and the code is executed the
这个单元格和代码被执行
same way as it is in the terminal or a
就像在航站楼里一样
Python script. This command here
Python 脚本 这里的命令
"%matplotlib inline" will render images
“% matplotlib inline”将呈现图像
generated with matplotlib in the
的 matplotlib 生成的
notebook instead of a separate window.
而不是一个单独的窗口
If the cell returns some output, you see here.
如果单元格返回一些输出 您可以看到这里
For instance, data. head() returns an HTML
例如 data.head ()返回一个 HTML
table displaying some of the data. Right
显示部分数据的表格
below here you see the data visualized
在这下面你可以看到数据的可视化
with a grid of scatter plots and
用散点图和网格
histograms. Notebooks even render math in
直方图 笔记本甚至可以呈现数学
a text cells.
文本单元格
This is just an example of what you can
这只是一个例子 你可以
do with notebooks. You have your code,
你有自己的代码,
documentation, visualizations, math, all in
文档 可视化 数学 都在里面
one place.
一个地方
Next, I'll show you how to use notebooks
接下来 我将向你们展示如何使用笔记本
in your workflow. It should take about an
在你的工作流程中
hour to get through the lesson, so see
一个小时来完成课程 所以看看
you in the classroom!
你在教室里！最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6